{
    "subject": "resource/Sarah_Kirsch_(poet)",
    "predicate": "property/dateOfBirth",
    "object": "1935-04-16",
    "human_readable": "Sarah Kirsch (poet) was born on April 16, 1935.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8786577582359314,
            "question": "When was Sarah Kirsch born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8784738183021545,
            "question": "Is April the month Sarah Kirsch was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8541735410690308,
            "question": "On what date was Sarah Kirsch born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7804926037788391,
            "question": "What is Sarah Kirsch's birthdate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7602707147598267,
            "question": "Is Sarah Kirsch a writer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6050014495849609,
            "question": "In what month and day was Sarah Kirsch born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5694875717163086,
            "question": "What profession is Sarah Kirsch known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46118882298469543,
            "question": "What year did Sarah Kirsch come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37786340713500977,
            "question": "What is Sarah Kirsch's area of expertise?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27050071954727173,
            "question": "What type of work is Sarah Kirsch known for creating?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sarah Kirsch (poet) was born on April 16, 1935.",
            "html": "dbpedia_787_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Sarah Kirsch's area of expertise?",
            "html": "dbpedia_787_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year did Sarah Kirsch come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_787_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What profession is Sarah Kirsch known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_787_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_787_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_787_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_787_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_787_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_787_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_787_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_787_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_787_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_787_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_787_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide consistent information that Sarah Kirsch was indeed born on April 16, 1935."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}